Birmingham raised me. I had a very Black experience. Black excellence was not a talented
10th kind of thing. It was like ubiquitous. My mayor was always Black. We had Black doctors,
principals, all those. It wasn't until I got older that I recognized just how abnormal that
experience was. And what it had done for me was that any room that I walked into,
and this may not be the most politically correct thing to say, but...
This is not a politically correct podcast.
I knew I was supposed to be there. And I actually believed that I likely had to be two or three
times better than a lot of other people in the room to even be in that space. So it allowed me
to just see myself and see my people in ways that I think are just different. Don't get me wrong,
we all got our bullshit, our insecurities, all the stuff. But having to shed my Blackness in
order to be excellent was never a thing.